<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on The blog of Heschlie</title>
    <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on The blog of Heschlie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 10:38:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.heschlie.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh what a wonderful weekend it was...</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2016/oh-what-a-wonderful-weekend-it-was/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 10:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2016/oh-what-a-wonderful-weekend-it-was/</guid>
      <description>This last weekend was quite exciting, made some major progress on building our new deck, but this post isn&amp;rsquo;t really about that, I&amp;rsquo;ll have a whole separate post with pictures, timelapse, etc&amp;hellip; once it is done. This post is about watercooled PCs and what happens when they fail!
So, sometime between Friday night and Saturday morning, my watercooler failed. The outlet on the pump (all in one type unit so the pump was on the CPU heatsink) broke off, not really sure how, and sprayed a water/glycol (I think?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New personal ventures</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/new-personal-ventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 08:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/new-personal-ventures/</guid>
      <description>Well it has been awhile since I posted last, lots of fun stuff going on but I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to keep it short. As I know some of the very few people who read this do not like walls of text, you know who you are&amp;hellip;
So a friend and I have decided to try and spin up a motorcycle show on YouTube in the style of Top Gear (or former Top Gear anyway) where it is mostly a satire of reviews, but not completely, if that makes sense?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week one down, tons more to go!</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/week-one-down-tons-more-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 08:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/week-one-down-tons-more-to-go/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve wrapped up my first week at the new Job, working on process control and automation for our research and development labs. I spent most of my week getting up to speed, as is the case with most new jobs. I have been able to make at least some contributions in my first week, but it will be some time until I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve made a real impact. The lab team was recently brought under the umbrella of IT, like in the past 2-3 months, and it is obviously making waves, and causing some slow down, but in my opinion it will be a change for the good as they will be able to benefit more from the IT side tools and people more than they would have before, but as with any major change it is slowing things down initially as people adjust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exciting times at the Schlie household</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/exciting-times-at-the-schlie-household/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 20:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/exciting-times-at-the-schlie-household/</guid>
      <description>Well we had a house party this last weekend and it all went very well, Whitney and I are now engaged and she is rocking on the wedding plans. We&amp;rsquo;re not even engaged for a week and she has already setup the venue, dates, and we have the wedding party planned, things are a movin! It was nice to have most of our friends and some of our family around for the event, I managed to keep it a secret from basically everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looks like I&#39;ll be joining the working world again</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/looks-like-ill-be-joining-the-working-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 15:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/looks-like-ill-be-joining-the-working-world-again/</guid>
      <description>Well it has been awhile since the layoffs at Riverbed, I&amp;rsquo;ve had many an interview but I was finally extended a formal offer, and the other two places that I had in mind fizzled out, so I&amp;rsquo;ll likely be taking this. The unfortunate part is I will be commuting down to San Jose from Concord again, in the end it isn&amp;rsquo;t horrible, I have some folks I will carpool with as they work down the road, so it will almost be like public transit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for something new</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/time-for-something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 08:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/time-for-something-new/</guid>
      <description>Well it has been a crazy week. We finalized the paperwork on a new house, which we will be moving into soon now, and within the same week I was laid off from my job in a large downsizing effort at Riverbed. This is an unfortunate turn of events, but I was given 2.5 months of severance to get back on my feet, and have already had a couple of good phone interviews.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>