<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automotive on The blog of Heschlie</title>
    <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/tags/automotive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Automotive on The blog of Heschlie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 08:49:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.heschlie.com/tags/automotive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New personal ventures</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/new-personal-ventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 08:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/new-personal-ventures/</guid>
      <description>Well it has been awhile since I posted last, lots of fun stuff going on but I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to keep it short. As I know some of the very few people who read this do not like walls of text, you know who you are&amp;hellip;
So a friend and I have decided to try and spin up a motorcycle show on YouTube in the style of Top Gear (or former Top Gear anyway) where it is mostly a satire of reviews, but not completely, if that makes sense?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another week almost done, and some new toys on the horizon</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/another-week-almost-done-and-some-new-toys-on-the-horizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 06:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/another-week-almost-done-and-some-new-toys-on-the-horizon/</guid>
      <description>Well it is almost the end of the week, I had some time before I get my day rolling in the office so I thought it would be a good time to do a thought dump while having my coffee.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been here for almost 2 weeks now, really starting to settle in and make this place feel like home. It is kind of weird not dreading going into the office every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exciting times at the Schlie household</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/exciting-times-at-the-schlie-household/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 20:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2015/exciting-times-at-the-schlie-household/</guid>
      <description>Well we had a house party this last weekend and it all went very well, Whitney and I are now engaged and she is rocking on the wedding plans. We&amp;rsquo;re not even engaged for a week and she has already setup the venue, dates, and we have the wedding party planned, things are a movin! It was nice to have most of our friends and some of our family around for the event, I managed to keep it a secret from basically everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>