<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hexo on The blog of Heschlie</title>
    <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/tags/hexo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hexo on The blog of Heschlie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 22:51:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.heschlie.com/tags/hexo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying Out Hugo</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2018/trying-out-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 22:51:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2018/trying-out-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Trying out Hugo for the blog Well I have had my eye on Hugo, a static site generator for some time now. It is written in Go, supports markdown, has a rich theme system, and as it says it generates html you can just drop in for nginx or whatever your webserver happens to be.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using hexo for some time now, and it has worked quite well, but I&amp;rsquo;m not fond of managing the Node dependencies, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know Javascript all too well so I wanted something that was both open source and written in a language I knew and could more easily contribute to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new Blog!</title>
      <link>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2017/a-new-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 20:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.heschlie.com/post/2017/a-new-blog/</guid>
      <description>Prepare for a boring post about blog software!
Heya Folks! I decided to try out a new blog software, I found myself wanting to write posts in something more MarkDown like, and Wordpress didn&amp;rsquo;t have very many good options for a MD editor with proper syntax highlighting. I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing a lot of MD for our git repos at Tigera, and code examples on Slack, and other places. I did some digging and came very close to grabbing Jekyll, but after some research I ended up landing on Hexo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>